{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "ich", "answer": "bin" },
    { "prompt": "du", "answer": "bist" },
    { "prompt": "er", "answer": "ist" },
    { "prompt": "sie", "answer": "ist" },
    { "prompt": "es", "answer": "ist" },
    { "prompt": "bin", "answer": "ich" },
    { "prompt": "bist", "answer": "du" },
    { "prompt": "ist", "answer": "er/sie/es" }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "ich", "answer": "habe" },
    { "prompt": "du", "answer": "hast" },
    { "prompt": "er", "answer": "hat" },
    { "prompt": "sie", "answer": "hat" },
    { "prompt": "es", "answer": "hat" },
    { "prompt": "habe", "answer": "ich" },
    { "prompt": "hast", "answer": "du" },
    { "prompt": "hat", "answer": "er/sie/es" }
  ]
}
